(Raj(Holds up finger to indicate he will be right back. Runs to kitchen. Tries to drink wine but bottle is empty. Looks in fridge and finds rum cake. Comes back stuffing a piece in his mouth):)Rum cake?
(Page:)No, thanks.
(Page:)Now, about Mr.
Wolowitz...
(Raj:)Seven years.
(Page:)I see.
(Raj:)I'm in this country
legally, you know.
(Page:)I'm sure you are.
(Page:)Now, to your knowledge, has Mr.
Wolowitz ever committed a crime?
(Raj:)Of course not.
(Raj:)I'm here on an H-1B visa,
(Raj:)which means I can't be
associated in any way
(Raj:)with crime
or criminal activity.
(Raj:)And I'm not.
(Howard:)Good.
(Page:)To your knowledge,
does Mr. Wolowitz
(Page:)have any foreign
contacts?
(Raj:)No, just me.
(Raj:)Oh, there it is.
(Raj:)Here comes a cavity search.
(Page:)Excuse me?
(Raj:)Please don't send me back
to India; it's so crowded!
(Raj:)It's like the whole country
is one endless Comic-Con,
(Raj:)except everybody's wearing
the same costume: Indian Guy.
(Page:)Dr. Koothrappali, I'm not...
I love this country!
(Raj:)The-the baseball,
the freedom,
(Raj:)the rampant morbid obesity!
(Raj:)From California
to the New York Island!
(Raj:)I'm a real Yankee Doodle boy!
(Woman at Door:)Dr. Koothrappali,
please.